<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="100">
    <author>Ritter</author>
    <version>1.1.0.1</version>
    <iconFilename>icon_TransactionLog.dds</iconFilename>
    <title>
        <en>Transaction log</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Transaction log

This mod adds a transaction log to the game, allowing you to keep track of all your financial transactions in a single place.
It includes features such as:
- Transaction Logging: Automatically tracks all financial transactions (income and expenses)
- Transaction combining: Groups frequent small transactions (landscaping, fuel purchase etc) to reduce log clutter.
- GUI Interface: View transaction history in an in-game dialog
- Transaction Details: Display ingame date/time, transaction type, amount, and current balance
- Add Comments: Edit and add custom comments to individual transactions
- Persistent Storage: Automatically save and load transaction data with your savegame
- Export to CSV: Export transaction history to CSV files in the mod settings directory for external analysis
- Clear Transaction Log: Remove all stored transactions with confirmation dialog

Default keybinding is Right Shift + T.

Source code and issue tracker at https://github.com/rittermod/FS25_TransactionLog


Changelog 1.1.0.1:
- Removed leftover debug loglevel setting to clean up log output.

Changelog 1.1.0.0:
- Transaction Log now supports automatic CSV export on daily, monthly, or yearly intervals configurable in the
  in-game settings menu. Auto-exports are saved with timestamped filenames (e.g., "auto_20241209" for daily) 
  and include transactions from the time period.

]]>        </en>
    </description>
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="scripts/RmTransactionLog.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <multiplayer supported="false"/>
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n" />
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="RM_SHOW_TRANSACTION_LOG">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rshift KEY_t"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
    <actions>
        <action name="RM_SHOW_TRANSACTION_LOG"/>
    </actions>
</modDesc>
